slideonline.com 2012-12-19

# SlideOnline.com

## Privacy

We are concerned about your privacy. Here are some important facts about our privacy policy.

We will never sell your personal information to any third party service or business for anything related to marketing purposes.

We will not disclosure your contact information with any 3rd party service without your consent.

We use industry standard protocols and technology to secure any sensitive inormation.

By submitting your presentations or templates to our website, thumbnail images can be generated and may appear online for other users. Since the presentations is not considered personally identifiable information, you are responsible for any sensitive information inside your slides.

Personal information collected by our site is limited to first name, last name, passwords and email address. Optionally, you can also specify your job position and other information that will be useful to configure your profile. 

Files that you decide to publish to our website are converted to a format suitable to be embedded in any web page. This process is done behind the scene. 

Your information will be kept under our databases during the period you have an account with us. If you ever want to delete your account then all your information will be permanently deleted from our records.

### Cookies

Our site uses cookies to track site usage. An Internet cookie is a tiny data file saved on your computer that allows us and our tools to recognize you as a user and know when you return to our site. This helps to customize certain sections of our site. You can disable cookies in your browser configuration, but our site needs cookies for some sections to proper function. Session Cookies will expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. As any other Internet service, we receive the IP of your connection. The relation between your IP address and your personally identifiable information will not be shared with any 3rd party service without your permission or except when required by law. Questions If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@slideonline.com
